https://www.ora4u.com/cookie-policy/

Skip to content
Cookie PolicyOra4u_admin2017-04-19T10:19:32+00:00
Privacy Policy
Here at ORA Squeegee, we value and respect your privacy. This page helps to explain what information we may gather about you, and how it may be utilised.
When you submit your details to us, through either the use of our forms or through direct e-mail, your information may be stored and used for our purposes to send out selected promotional e-mails.
From this information gathered, we will only use the information for the business uses of ORA Squeegee, and its brands, and your details will not be passed on or sold to any third parties.
Cookie Policy
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. These files can be used to record information about how you have used the site, and can help us to improve the site and make it work more efficiently. For more information on cookies please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ or download the ICC UK Cookie Guide.
How this site uses cookies
Our website collects only anonymous data for analytic purposes and this information does not enable us to identify individual users. No data that we collect is shared with third parties.
Whilst you are able to access our website without the use of cookies, it may hinder your site experience.
Below is a breakdown of the cookies that you may encounter on this site.
Cookie
Name
Purpose
More info
Google Analytics
__utma
__utmb
__utmc
__utmz
We use these to collect information about how visitors use our site. This information is used to improve the site.
These cookies collect anonymous information about visitors, such as whether you have what pages have been visited, and the number of visitors to the site.
Google Privacy Policy
http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html
Google Analytics Opt Out Add-on
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en
PHPSESSID
This cookie does not contain any personal data, and is an essential cookie to help the site run efficiently. It is deleted at the end of each session.
CIVIC UK
civicAllowCookies
civicShowCookieIcon
Cookie Control cookies. These cookies are set in order to remember preferences in regards to cookies.
LinkedIn
x-li-ibc
x-li-ddc
bcookie
leo-auth-token
in_hash
JSESSIONID
visit
l1e
These are third party cookies used by LinkedIn see if you are following the company page on LinkedIn.
LinkedIn Privacy Policy
www.linkedin.com/static?key=privacy_policy
Twitter
guest_id
twll
remember_checked
k
lang
js
_twitter_sess
These are third party cookies used by Twitter see if you are following the company page on Twitter.
Twitter Privacy Policy
https://twitter.com/privacy
Embedded content
To highlight the some of the products and their benefits, and to enhance your access to information, we may embed content from external websites such as YouTube (for videos) and YUDU (for catalogues). By doing so, when you access one of the pages which shares this content, you may encounter cookies from these websites. These cookies are not controlled by ORA Squeegee; therefore you should check the relevant third party’s website for more information.
YUDU – http://free.yudu.com/info/privacy-policy
YouTube – http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/
Controlling your cookie consent
To assist with your management of your cookie control, we have implemented a tool, which you should see in the bottom left of the website, enabling you to disable cookies used on this website.
E-mail Newsletters
If you have received one of our e-mail newsletters, you may some additional cookies to enable us to track the open rates of e-mails. They also allow us to track the interest levels of our newsletters to ensure we are only sending out relevant information. These only work if you have downloaded the images. All our e-mail newsletters have the option to unsubscribe, so if not no longer wish to receive these e-mails you can easily unsubscribe from the list.
Toggle Sliding Bar Area
English
Contact Europe
Owen Price
Sales Executive
(44) 1594 847 169
owenprice@wattspu.co.uk
Asia
We use cookies to improve our site and your experience    Find out more.Okay, thanks
